Expanding is the task of taking a shorter piece of text
扩写是指将一篇较短的文本进行扩写的工作
such as a set of instructions or a list of topics
如一套指示或一个主题列表
and having the large language model generate a longer piece of text
并让大语言模型生成一个较长的文本
such as an email or an essay about some topic
例如一封电子邮件或一篇关于某些主题的文章
There are some great uses of this
这方面有一些很好的用途
such as if you use a large language model as a brainstorming partner
例如，如果你使用一个大语言模型作为头脑风暴的伙伴
But I just also want to acknowledge that there's
但是，我也想承认，有一些
some problematic use cases of this
有问题的使用案例
such as if someone were to use it to generate a large amount of spam
例如，如果有人用它来产生大量的垃圾邮件
So when you use these capabilities of a large language model
因此，当你使用大语言模型的这些能力时
please use it only in a responsible way and in a way that helps people
请以负责任的方式和帮助人们的方式来使用它
In this video, we'll go through an example of how you can use
在这个视频中，我们将通过一个例子来说明
a language model to generate a personalized email based on some information
如何使用语言模型，生成一个基于某些信息的个性化电子邮件
The email is kind of self-proclaimed to be from an AI bot
这封邮件自称是来自一个AI机器人
which as Andrew mentioned, is very important
正如恩达提到的，这一点非常重要
We're also going to use another one of
我们还将使用另一个
the model's input parameters called temperature
该模型的另一个输入参数，叫做temperature（温度）
and this allows you to vary the degree of
这允许你改变模型的探索和多样性的程度
exploration and variety in the model's responses
这允许你改变模型响应的探索和多样性
So let's get into it
因此，让我们开始吧
So before we get started
在我们开始之前
we're going to do the usual setup
我们要做一些常规的设置
So set up the OpenAI Python package
所以要设置OpenAI Python软件包
and then also define our helper function, get_completion
然后定义我们的辅助函数，get_completion
Now we're going to write a custom email response to a customer review
现在我们要为客户的评论写一个自定义的电子邮件回复
So given a customer review and the sentiment
所以给定一个客户评论和情绪
we're going to generate a custom response
我们将生成一个自定义的回复
Now we're going to use the language model to generate
现在我们要使用语言模型来生成
a custom email to a customer based on a customer review
根据客户的评论，给客户发送一封定制的电子邮件
and the sentiment of the review
和评论的情绪
So we've already extracted the sentiment
所以我们已经提取了情绪
using the kind of prompts that we saw in the inferring video
使用我们在推理视频中看到的那种提示
and then this is the customer review for a blender
然后这就是客户对搅拌机的评论
Now we're going to customize the reply based on the sentiment
现在我们要根据情感来定制回复
So here the instruction is
所以这里的指令是
you are a customer service AI assistant
你是一个客户服务的AI助理
Your task is to send an email reply to a valued customer
你的任务是给一个有价值的客户发送电子邮件回复
Given the customer email delimited by three backticks
给出客户的电子邮件，以三个`符号分割
generate a reply to thank the customer for their review
产生一个回复，以感谢客户的评论
If the sentiment is positive or neutral
如果情绪是积极的或中性的
thank them for their review
感谢他们的评论
If the sentiment is negative
如果情绪是负面的
apologize and suggest that they can reach out to customer service
道歉，并建议他们可以联系客户服务部
Make sure to use specific details from the review
确保使用评论中的具体细节
write in a concise and professional tone
用简明和专业的语气来写
and sign the email as AI customer agent
并以AI客户代理的身份在邮件中签名
When you're using a language model
当你使用一个语言模型
to generate text that you're going to show to a user
来生成你要展示给用户的文本
it's very important to have this kind of transparency
有这样的透明度是非常重要的
and let the user know that the text they're seeing was generated by AI
并让用户知道他们看到的文本是由AI生成的
Then we'll just input the customer review and the review sentiment
然后我们就输入客户的评论和评论的情绪
Also note that this part isn't necessarily important
还要注意，这部分不一定很重要
because we could actually use this prompt to also extract the review sentiment
因为我们实际上也可以使用这个提示来提取评论的情绪
and then in a follow-up step, write the email
然后在后续步骤中，编写电子邮件
But just for the sake of the example
但是，只是为了这个例子的目的
well, we've already extracted the sentiment from the review
好吧，我们已经从评论中提取了情感
So here we have a response to the customer
所以在这里我们有一个给客户的回复
It addresses details that the customer mentioned in their review
它涉及客户在评论中提到的细节
and as we instructed
并且按照我们的指示
suggest that they reach out to customer service
建议他们与客户服务部联系
because this is just an AI customer service agent
因为这只是一个AI客户服务代理
Next, we're going to use a parameter of the language model called temperature
接下来，我们将使用语言模型的一个参数，叫做temperature
that will allow us to change the variety of the model's responses
这将使我们能够改变模型响应的多样性
So you can think of temperature as
所以你可以把temperature看成
the degree of exploration or randomness of the model
模型的探索或随机性的程度
So for this particular phrase
因此，对于这个特定的短语
my favorite food is
我最喜欢的食物是
the most likely next word that the model predicts is pizza
模型预测的最有可能的下一个词是披萨
and the next two most likely
而接下来的两个最可能的
it suggests are sushi and tacos
它建议是寿司和玉米饼
So at a temperature of zero
因此，在temperature为零的情况下
the model will always choose the most likely next word
模型总是会选择最可能的下一个词
which in this case is pizza
在这个例子中是比萨
and at a higher temperature
而在更高的temperature下
it will also choose one of the less likely words
它也会选择一个不太可能的词
and at an even higher temperature
甚至在更高的temperature下
it might even choose tacos
它有可能选择玉米饼
which only has a five percent chance of being chosen
虽然这只有5%的机率被选中
You can imagine that as the model continues this final response
你可以想象，当模型继续这个最后的响应
so my favorite food is pizza
所以我最喜欢的食物是比萨饼
and it continues to generate more words
而且它继续产生更多的词
this response will diverge from the first response
这个响应会与第一个响应发生分歧
which is my favorite food is tacos
也就是我最喜欢的食物是玉米饼
So as the model continues
所以随着模型的继续
these two responses will become more and more different
这两个响应将变得越来越不同
In general, when building applications where you want
一般来说，在构建你想要的应用程序时
a predictable response
一个可预测的响应
I would recommend using temperature zero
我建议使用temperature=0
Throughout all of these videos
在所有这些视频中
we've been using temperature zero
我们一直在使用temperature=0
and I think that if you're trying to build a system that
我认为，如果你试图建立一个系统
is reliable and predictable, you should go with this
可靠和可预测的系统，你应该使用这个
If you're trying to use the model in a more creative way
如果你想以更有创意的方式使用这个模型
where you might want a wider variety of different outputs
你可能希望有更多不同的输出
you might want to use a higher temperature
你可能想用更高的temperature
So now let's take this same prompt that we just used
那么，现在让我们把刚才的提示也拿出来
and let's try generating an e-mail
让我们试着生成一封电子邮件
but let's use a higher temperature
但让我们使用一个更高的temperature
So in our get_completion function that we've been using throughout the videos
所以在我们的get_completion函数中，我们在整个视频中一直在使用
we have specified a model and then also a temperature
我们已经指定了一个模型和一个temperature
but we've set them to default
但我们已经把它们设置为默认值
So now let's try varying the temperature
所以现在让我们试着改变temperature
So we use the prompt
所以我们使用提示
and then let's try temperature=0.7
然后让我们试试temperature=0.7
And so with temperature=0
于是用temperature=0
every time you execute the same prompt
每次你执行同样的提示时
you should expect the same completion
你应该期待同样的完成
whereas with temperature 0.7
而在temperature为0.7时
you'll get a different output every time
你每次都会得到一个不同的输出
So here we have our e-mail
所以这里我们有我们的电子邮件
and as you can see, it's different to the e-mail
正如你所看到的，它与我们之前收到的电子邮件
that we received previously
不同
And let's just execute it again to show that we'll get a different e-mail again
让我们再执行一次，以显示我们将再次得到一个不同的电子邮件
And here we have another different e-mail
这里我们有另一封不同的电子邮件
So I recommend that you play around with temperature yourself
所以我建议你自己玩一下temperature
Maybe you could pause the video now and try this prompt
也许你现在可以暂停视频，并尝试这个提示
with a variety of different temperatures
用各种不同的temperature
just to see how the outputs vary
只是为了看看输出是如何变化的
So to summarize, at higher temperatures
因此，总结一下，在较高的temperature下
the outputs from the model are kind of more random
模型的输出更加随机
You can almost think of it as that at higher temperatures
你几乎可以认为，在较高temperature下
the assistant is more distractible
助理更容易分心
but maybe more creative
但也许更有创造力
In the next video, we're going to talk more about
在下一个视频中，我们将进一步讨论
the chat completions endpoint format
对话补全终端格式
and how you can create a custom chatbot using this format
以及你如何使用这种格式创建一个自定义的聊天机器人